

Dimitar Petkov

Address: Sadovo 4122, Plovdiv, Bulgaria

Phone: +359 877 531 204 E-mail: mitfreex@gmail.com

Summary:

After many years working in advertising and print products and services, I decided to start a new career path. Two years ago I begin studying software development at SoftUni. I have successfully completed through in-depth vanilla javascript courses. After that I learned basic skills for frameworks like Express for back-end, Angular and React for front-end. As a junior front-end developer with no professional experience, it would be a worthwhile challenge for me to get into your project where I will surely have the opportunity to face real working problems, tasks, concepts and learn professional approaches to solve them in team collaboration.

Work experience:

• 2006 - 2007

Organizer Warehouse at INDEX-6 Ltd Plovdiv

description:

Monitoring stock of purchase items, working with warehouse program, ordering, planning.

• 2008 - 2018

DTP operator

at **FOART**

advertising agency / studio (Plovdiv)

description:

File processing, preparation, assembly for printing in software environment: Adobe Indesign/ Illustrator/ Photoshop, PDF Acrobat professional; Corel Draw. Preparation of files for digital printing, offset printing, screen printing. Printing on digital printer + finishing processes. Bidding for clients. Communication with subcontractors. Organizing and tracking order fulfillment.

• 2018 - 2022 DTP operator

at DSN-Sofia Brand Quadergy

description:

Artwork preparation of packaging files for printing. Processing and content adaptation of packaging files for food and cosmetics of global brands such as Danone and Unilever.

Education:

• 1996 - 2001

Ivan Vazov Language High School Plovdiv

• 2001 - 2005

Technical University of Sofia -

Plovdiv Branch

Bachelor Engineer

Automation Information and Control Engineering

2022 - present

Software University Itd.

https://softuni.bg

JS developer

certificates:

Angular:

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/212772/e521e42b **REACT:**

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/170045/93bcf246 **JS Advanced:**

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/145439/3f75f3d3 JS Application:

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/181858/4f838437 **JS Back-End:**

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/199626/060c1758 **HTML, CSS:**

https://softuni.bg/certificates/details/213549/25685e92

• links to some projects: https://github.com/Mitpf/trips-offers https://github.com/Mitpf/car-service

Skills:

Adobe software: Ilustrator, Photoshop, Indesign

Software development: Vanilla Javascript, HTML/CSS, JS frameworks/libraries: Express, REACT, Angular